hello everyone
well I just bought a vacuum cleaner a
few of you asked me what Instagram
should I do a reveal so well here is it
this is I bought a DVR the value V
vacuum cleaner for a purpose of my so
far because I bought a so far that I did
not realize I can take the cover off to
wash it so yeah so what is to do my
pitch signal zone and also the curtain
so one of the reason I bought this
because I saw a video of the YouTube
hood Joseph Germany he says quite good
and he shows a review that well these
packages reached quite fast all
avoidable asada and it takes about 10
days comes with another box of carbon
box that pretends this package and it's
my procedure so let's do the unboxing
in here they have a user manual well the
problem is well here mention instruction
manual but when you flip it is all in
Chinese well I'm a banana so I can
really read Chinese thing if they have
pictures that line for you
well good thing we really need this we
just go it we just do any tools
they have one of this this is a dust
collection filter I believe and inspect
it like that it's quite people so like
that so you need to buy an additional
clock clock on it because this this
thing is from China
so here you go how it looks like it
looks like a gray poodle and I think
this is the UV light section then they
have the process
okay and I don't watch these oh that's a
wheeler
there is about the new
you can pick this up to change the field
ugly
our wedding dissolve looks like it looks
like it's being still
but configure up can this be open
because I the fryin here doesn't seems
like we can unlock
to yourself not too sure what's this for
misery
nope it looks like it can be open from
the fire so I think from the back I have
no idea what is it all about this needs
of chili to you guys
[Music]
well this is my sofa well 1940 stand
already well I really plug it in
the huge main problem now means I don't
know watch this puppet fall and I don't
know what's this button for we will test
it out
one good thing is that the wine is quite
long I plug it into my bubble over there
and I think it's good enough to move
around my 11 feet so far let's start
using it well a phony this is the on/off
button
jeez I'm not to show is it I thing is on
of the UV light let's check it out
[Music]
[Applause]
so I'm crying to this vacuum
cleaner yes you can see just now start
off with the clean one is unbox pack and
I'm not too sure can you see a lot of
dots in there oops there might be a
reflection yep
it's actually collected quite a lot of
gas
I've done my sofa I'm gonna check it
I'll show you how much - I think like
that this is just a brand new and I just
took it out and I just finished
vacuuming my hole so far and let's see
what had been captured well you can see
among us it's quite thick no I can't
really show you but then there is a lot
of dust let me see how can I do it
well let's start from behind I think
this will be the easiest part you can
see there's a dots of dark spots
that's the dust collected from my sofa
and you will be impressed on how this
thing works
change engine you see this is all from
my so far
quite impressive - on the amount of
darks it have collected and in here they
have a bit of dusting that I think you
can see that a little bit on the far top
on the end and at the bottom and you can
see a layer of dust yep there you this
is all from my cushion dust collector
quite good
well oh I found out what does this
button do is actually a turbocharged
it's like if the suction is not strong
enough you just press this it doubles up
the power
I'll show you know I only can see the
blue light that's the UV light
thank you
the UV light do not touch it fighting
with them it's not good for our skin
Derek the safety button you can pick it
up there's also on/off key goes in the
error to a 7c uni will light back up
again so can you hear this action it's
quite loud Oh
and let one leaf
Oh actually leave nothing in October
finally building the vibrating
he's like thousand beats per second
I thing is for heavy suction that you
need it like to beat the little area
than to let it suck more on that well
let's do it on my carpet let's see what
how much dust can you collect all right
[Music]
even more tha's absolutely nice
well that's more dust now yeah yeah well
D just not show you is on my sofa
no it's after my carpet there's more
dust and in 2mm and it's more prominent
I wonder does one good thing is that I
bought this uni because of the UV light
well this thing is not too bad and I
think is worried it's because that the
original price was 240 if I remember
correctly and I got this at a very good
party it was during a town hall special
sale I was three diesel and then I miss
it then after that I wait for the 99 and
the price was down 268 this thing is
hundred sixty-eight so I got no
complaint at all and it's free delivery
from all the way to China so well for
handheld vacuum cleaner I think it's
quite powerful the only sane thing is
you've got this wiring it's not Wireless
or battery charge so you gotta plug to
the nearest checkpoint that you have if
your house is big then you need to get
an extension and overall this is not a
killer material it's because that I
bought this and a post Instagram and
some of you asked to review this product
and hence dangle so the next purchase I
think you guys are not you know how are
you buy one wait for 1111 the singles
details I believe will be much cheaper
or it could be the price that I'm
getting so for women I think it might be
too heavy for you there are a few units
I check it out that they do have a
lighter version but it slightly more
expensive so it really depends on you
what you're preparing if you like
something cheap and it's not - Oh poppy
I think this is for the salary there are
a few other brands that I saw I was
Hindu by on another Korean brand but I
bought this because of the price factor
the other foreign brain is much lighter
and it cost about 250 plus of the system
and compared to hydrogen
of course this we know I can get it
bargain or 100 near 200 near Sydney so
well not a publicity but it is a review
for you guys for you guys to decide
right do you want to get it or don't
want to get it but to me I'm happy with
it well thanks for watching this is my
first product review that I did in the
video so if it's not too good that I'm
sorry but it's just for all my friends
to get a reference of this product so if
you like to me to have more product
reviews I'll try to do some other
program reviews or like this water every
spot is from Co me it's called a miss me
I'll be doing the next review on this
watch which is I think a good party
[Music]